Calvin Chun Hin Bochyński-Ng PhD BEng

Software Engineer - Web Developer

Summary

Eager and enthusiastic software engineer - web developer with a focus on building a better accessible digital experience for all users. PhD in Electronic Engineering with 5 years of industrial experience in RF Antenna Engineering.

calvinng1993@gmail.com +44 7840 073033 github.com/calvin-bochynski-ng linkedin.com/in/calvinbochynsking/ calvin.bochynski-ng.com

Projects

Portfolio

FEB 2024

 Utilising Next.js and Tailwind CSS to create a responsive website to showcase all the projects with a dark mode theme switcher. Using tsparticles for subtle background movement to create a dynamic feel to the webpage.

Mapplar

JAN - FEB 2024 | CAPSTONE

 Mapbox integration and precise OpenAl prompts to generate compelling and accurate itineraries for users. Using firebase for cloud storage and a robust user authentication system with JWT token for security and efficiency.

Acabo

JAN 2024 | HACKATHON Industrial project (Deliveroo) - 5 PERSON (24 Hours)

 Managing between UX/UI and SE, relay information and making critical design choices to project deadline within strict timeframe, using JIRA to assign tasks and managing Pull Requests to ensure a cohesive workflow

Debug Ducky

JAN 2024 | HACKATHON Pair Programming - 2 PERSON (24 Hours)

 Managed Back-end operations, developing RESTful endpoints using Express framework. Using Postman for verification of outcomes, validating against sample inputs to ensure alignment with expected results.

Star Wars Yearbook

NOV 2023 | HACKATHON - 2 PERSON (5 Hours)

 Managed the styling of the web applications, selecting optimal fonts and following best practices in BEM naming conventions. Collaborated with team members using Git Flow to ensure seamless integration and prevent conflicts.

Experience

Senior Antenna Engineer | Leonardo UK

AUG 2023 - NOV 2023 | Luton, United Kingdom

- Design and develop antennas & radomes for funtion and RCS
- Nominated and Recieved an award for Technology and Innovation

Microwave and Antenna Engineer | Meta Material Inc

JUN 2022 - JUL 2023 | London

- Conference paper accepted IEEE APS 2023
- Lead and manage various antenna design projects
- · Combine RF technologies with metamaterial for R&D

Senior Antenna RF Design Engineer | Airbus

SEPT 2018 - JUN 2022 | Stevenage, Hertfordshire

- Accountable for the transmit antenna on a satellite platform
- Developed algorithms to improve productivity across the team.
- Participate in and manage proposal activities

RF Design Engineer | Omni-ID

APR 2018 - SEPT 2018 | Farnham, Surrey

- · Understanding RFID both in Hardware and Software
- · Producing a commercially ready RFID Tag used for plant trolleys.

Skills

Programming Languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Sass, SQL, C, MATLAB

Libraries and Frameworks

React, Next.js, Node.js, Express. js, Tailwind CSS, Mapbox, Firebase, OpenAl, material UI, Next UI

Tools and Design

Bash, Terminal, Git & GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Chrome Dev Tools, Postman, Jira, MySQL, Figma, InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effect, Premier Pro

Education

Diploma - Software Engineer | BrainStation

NOV 2023 - FEB 2024 | London

- Learning industry best practices throughout the course to become a proficient software developer.
- Developing foundational skills in web development, progressing from basic multi-page web design to advanced Single Page Application development using React.
- Back-end development with technologies such as Node.js and Express, effectively setting up frameworks and utilising MySQL databases for seamless data management and persistence.

Doctor of Philosophy - Electronic Engineering | University of Kent

SEPT 2014 - JUL 2019 | Canterbury, Kent

 "Applications of Origami Folding Techniques of Antenna Structures using Flexible Substrates"

Bachelor of Engineering - Electronic and Communciations Engineering | University of Kent

SEPT 2011 - JUL 2014 | Canterbury, Kent

Hobbies

Badminton, Cycling, Volleyball, Bouldering, Web Design, Picture and Video editing, Gaming